{
    "id": "bd856057bc0744d5b6f85b396ca53243",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have real trouble getting on ……………………. my landlady.",
            "description": "To get on with somebody is to maintain good relation with them. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "with",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich man looks down ………………………….. his poor neighbors.",
            "description": "To look down upon somebody is to consider them inferior. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest gave …………………. the prizes.",
            "description": "To give away the prizes is to distribute the prizes.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you don’t know the meaning of a word, you should look it ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher was very popular among her students and they all looked ……………………… to her.",
            "description": "To look up to somebody is to have a great deal of respect for them.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The bridge gave …………………………. under the weight of heavy traffic.",
            "description": "Give way can mean collapse. ",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "way",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He could not put ………………………….. with such an insult.",
            "description": "To put up with insult is to tolerate it. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was put ……………………………. when he refused to listen to her.",
            "description": "To put somebody out is to annoy them. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must put ………………………… something for the rainy day.",
            "description": "Put by can mean save an amount to use later. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "by",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She could not see ………………………….. his game.",
            "description": "When you can see through something you can detect the true nature of it. ",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "at",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The twin girls take ………………………….. their mother.",
            "description": "Take after = resemble",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "after",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager took him …………………………… task.",
            "description": "To take somebody to task is to rebuke them. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}